So I see Grenada is considering allowing the United States to utilize the Maurice Bishop Airport as a site for military operations against Venezuela.
Mind you, all accusations of the United States have made against Venezuela and Maduro are completely made up.
There is absolutely no proof or any level of evidence to show that this man is some head of some cartel.
Venezuela is not even a drug-producing country.
This is all for oil.
Notre Dame and Tobago has already capitulated and allowed for military exercises to take place on their island.
Grenada, I'm begging you, please, please do not allow this to happen.
Please do not mistake any dealings with the government of the United States as anything that's going to be useful to the Spice Island.
It would be a grave, grave error that would forever shape the future of the Spice Isle in a deeply harmful way.
Grenadians, please drop your flags in the comments and share your thoughts.
You're damn rude, eh?